Shanti, Madhyama Vaikari,
Four rivers of sound spill from her mouth.
Three are unseen, one becomes the world.
Add faint heart beat drum, and on a bass pulse drop.
You
Is eating static whispering your eyes and traffic they crawl through my circuits chanting reverse like angels that flunk their universe
I'm sorry. I'm just saying you can go check out my website if you want. It is up but it's not like
finished. It will be and I think I shouldn't like even be promoting before but it's like
mostly done and I'm certainly impressed how far it's gone. I think it has most everything set up
but for some reason anything doesn't work just let me know. Hi baby. Would you like to watch the page
Are you ready?
Yeah, what's up?
Thank you so much for watching.
You can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me, you can't do that to me
I'm a little bit proud of me.
at least it'll be maybe like you know maybe like four or five people instead of like you know 20
25 people you know what it's better than nobody and i'm not monetized so what does it matter where
i'm playing what let me take down my channel i have other ones like ready to go
you would have DMCA strike my website.
Oh, oh, will you?
Like, that what we did last time?
You know, I already went through this with you
with 11 times and I went through lawyers
and you know, all these legal documents.
And I know exactly the whole key to everything, okay?
That's, that you're just mostly full of shit.
Like 90% of the time.
You're not worth, you know, filing any police report.
You're not worth like, you know, you're just worth,
you know.
imagining you like, you know, boiling an excrement.
That's what I, that's what I like to imagine you as.
You're just sitting under a bridge as in your real troll form.
And it's hideous.
Like you think God, you call me Cyrax.
I mean, it's like, you look like a Cyrax exploded.
I mean, I mean, it's like, you look, you make Cyrax's,
you know, tooth look like the Mona Lisa or something like that.
He just knows like Michael Jackson, okay?
And his hairline, it looks normal.
I'm sorry, it's 2.0.
What, does that mean you're gonna prove though?
It's like, well, is that any of your business?
This isn't my work.
Like this guy's trying to distract.
I'm gonna try to turn my text messages.
Unfortunately, I have to keep it on for the police
because they're tracing these calls and so.
But anyway, I'm gonna play a copyrights. Oh, it's an un-copyrights. Oh, one second. I
Love this video. I
Hope you do
Oh my gosh it's talking about world politics. Hey guys, I mean it's like yeah, this guy
He's like trying to like you know hurt me and stuff and it's like it's no matter what he does
I'm just gonna get better. It's like I always try hard
Makes me that much stronger makes me work a little bit harder
I'm sorry
But there's like a Christina Aguilar a song that pretty much sums up how I feel I don't know
I might make an AI Perry of it. I'm not sure
I don't know what it would be. I mean, I already have the I'm getting stronger. I love it. I'm getting stronger. So it's so catchy
I mean, it's like that's a secret to like music is like
It being catchy
Because it's like you hear something like and then it's like
It repeats this a few times and it's like an NSA, especially if it like hits in certain ways
I don't know. It's like all these different parts of the brain are both. That's why I definitely know the whole like, you know
People study it in Tabasuck Institute. Do you guys hear me at all? Okay. Anyway, I'm gonna play this nice cute little video
No, I mean, I don't have to worry about like, you know playing these videos and see oh my gosh
It's just taking me off to this like Saudi Arabian thing. Oh, I don't want to look at some of this one
Stop
This is Halloween is this a Halloween prank guys, what are you doing to me guys? Are you know like, you know, we're gonna this day
Okay home
Okay, here
You'll love this. Well, I don't know if you'll love it. I've played it a few times before
You know Jamaica is the new Lahaina. I don't know what that means, but isn't that interesting?
Okay, so here we go just sit back and relax and just listen to beautiful music. Oh shit
Yeah, but I'll call you right back. Okay. I'm on the show. Okay. Thank you so much. Thank you officer. Bye
Okay
Anyway, okay
So, let's see, do you know this about okay, so here's a song enjoy
Copyright this um
Benjamin
Whatever your last name is cow
Are you going to hear it?
Oh, sure.
Got you.
I am asking your help in the tremendous task of informing and alerting the American people.
What we are opposed around the world by a monolithic and ruthless conspiracy,
have been lies primarily on coveted means, on infiltration instead of invasion.
Now hold them in the world. Now hold the powers, Dave. That's the point.
They said Yanko was the only great chip that controlled the whole society.
I could get you lit up
One of two ways, what's it gonna be?
That was irreversible. This was not an election. This was a revolution.
This was an irregular warfare at its finest.
We have what we call citizen journalists. We have an army of digital soldiers.
You're here because you've made a decision about something in your life.
You can't sit back. You have a responsibility.
One spoonful of honey with cinnamon before bed equals zero memory collapse.
Oh my god, was I not even on the stage? Hold on, hold on, was I on now or on your move?
I'm very confused, am I on now? Oh, there I am, okay.
Um, anyway, let's uh, I'll play like a couple more songs, you guys are just like wanting to hear
the songs so bad, right? Let me see.
Hello, it's halo ween. It's halo. It's halo ween. You know that it's a cute joke
I'm sorry didn't do a halo. I'm moticon though. That would have been cool, but um
You know, hey, hello, happy halloween. I don't know what it means to you, but
Sorry, I just got really excited to say that. Oh my gosh, is my microphone not working. What's going on here?
Okay. Oh, you notice I get good
Okay, let's do
I have a song about Halo 2, I don't know if I played it earlier, but I was just gonna play, okay, let's see, I mean we have the Nixle, oh yeah, I was gonna try this other version of this audio, yeah, do you guys hear me okay?
I don't know. I'm actually sitting on the floor. I don't know why. I'm just gonna take it off.
But uh, I'll momentarily, okay, so let me see. This is great. Let's test this out.
And I think, how much coffee do I have left? I still have a little bit of coffee left.
You guys enjoy this
Be drum and on a bay
me in the sun or the horror movies. I'm just kidding. I'm not trying to hide. Is that me?
Hold on. Oh, that's my picture. I thought I was, like, standing very, very still. I'm just
confused. Okay, let me see. Okay, so I keep my only gate, but I can't lose my LGBTQ token.
You're calling me an object, but it's not even like an object worthy of being called a currency. It's basically a token. It's like, oh, yeah, again, it's like, you know, it's sort of like called slow. It just takes, you know, they're not really worth anything. They're just tokens. So just like, you know, just like, like, oh, it looks like, it looks like a coin, but it's just always worth zero.
That's why that's what I'm that's what I'm to you. I'm just like the affirmative action and that's why people need if you needed me
The why?
important bombing me and attacking all the time and hate and hating me
I'm going to twist your words because
You know, you don't do anything except like, you know talk a lot of jive turkey shit to me
You never like hit on me or anything. It's like I'm
I needed him to like meet, what romance have I had on the show this year, okay? Listen, what?
Meezer? He was disgusting. I mean, it's like, I would never date Meezer. I mean, it's like, oh my god.
I mean, that's the only person that was even interested to me in the whole, in the whole panel verse.
And maybe, I think maybe Tony, Tony likes me.
I mean I don't know it's like only explanation I have is that he's like in love with me or
he is like so in love with me that he's going to you know take out a lot of people trying to
I don't I don't know I just see I just see I just want him to stay like I stayed away I
Yeah, I know why I'm so sorry what happened KZ. Oh my gosh, where's what coming from it's a stage
This stage. What are you talking about?
No one's laughing. I know you're why don't hear you guys laugh
That's why I don't know if you're laughing or not
You could all just be sitting in silence judgemental looks on your face. Is that me? I would never know the difference
You don't sound very nice when you call in your girl. You're all most most of your terrible
Whether it's Alexander talking too loud KZ, you know, sounding like he's you know calling from Atlantis
And then you know
God he calling every you know nice nice lady that comes on a big fat cow and scaring everyone away
What am I supposed to do?
You're always nice to me
I know if they say you're supposed to like hit on me a little bit because that I mean it's like I
People are nice. It's like that's not very like
Like, oh wow, it'd be nice. It's just like fake, you know, it's like I want somebody I want you to be like
Hey psyche and then like, you know come like, you know taking me to dinner and like, you know
I give you like a great blowjob and then we still be a cuddle together
That's all I thought I'm interested in
It saves that okay
You can't stream in a blow job. We can't stream the aftermath of the dinner. I think that is. How are you? You found me?
And then it's got me. Oh my gosh. I was trying to hide from you
I changed the name of the cult and everything changed the name I moved to stay away and look you figured it out Canadian intelligence
I'm telling you there's something to it guys
And I don't mean just the smart Canadian people. I mean like the actual intelligence agency in Canada. I'm just kidding
Okay
Well, he thing that is invited you to a diddy party last night. Oh, why aren't I included in some of these?
I was sitting here alone like
You know nothing else to do. Well, why was it I included in a diddy party?
No, not not even the ones to me to be at my own like I remember like I went like
To on this trip and I was like kind of like more my dorky face
I was like probably 15 years old and I was like I was with all these high schoolers and stuff like that and
and big
we got kind of like all bonded but it's like I was kind of like just so dorky and like and
whatever they tolerated me but uh at the end of it they were like playing strip poker one day
and I was like how to play strip poker and then it's like they all I think I think that they just
ended the game or something like that was just like they're like no it was like it was just like
there no one was interested anyway um and then um
Yeah, that's pretty much my normal experiences. It's been pretty oily. Uh-oh, Arbiter pretty oily, you said. Ooh, Yard. Ooh.
Do you want to oil me up, Arbiter?
You can.
You noticed my channel link? Oh, you dropped my channel link? Oh, thank you, Shimei. Oh, come on. Yes, a few chats. Okay.
The state arbiter you're having, is it lit?
No, it's not gonna be lit.
Those are either go blackmail parties
where they make you do sexual stuff against your will.
Don't you know about those?
It's like you have to call it something else
and then put a safer twist on it than the name Diddy party.
I think Diddy is kind of not a good brand anymore.
Remember that Sean John,
is anyone wearing Sean John anymore?
I don't know.
Has anyone been buying like the Junior Mafia albums?
Or what's his last, Sean Combs' last hit?
That's just the way it is.
What was it?
Ain't no pod, like a ghost party.
You're, oh yeah.
Okay, let's play the ghost song.
Yes.
However, before it was, it's just a perfect technique.
Take a little breather.
Would you like to hear the ghost song, everybody?
Oh, you would?
Okay, I'm gonna play it right now.
You're in luck.
By my grandmother, he goes to life
Let my love fucking go
May I have permission to crash out?
Ghost already did it to the heart
That goes through the night
That's how you know the haunts alive
Lights flicker
Chats in the right
And somewhere goes about to die
Heroes are loud like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks, cracking jokes
Keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts howling
I was reborn may I have permission to crush
Psych is proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud
Such a dull flame
May I have permission to crash out?
The ones who doubt
I was like talking this whole time
and you missed all my jokes.
That's so terrible.
But again, if anyone's criticizing me,
my eyes just glaze over and I'm just like,
fuck you, you don't know what I'm going through
or what I've been through is like having channels
and I have to go through it, okay?
And it's like, and that's your help in me?
Which like, you know, people,
someone like so many people like to criticize,
poor ghost, poor sweet ghost is like one of the only people
that is, you know,
And there's a few other people that are really special to me.
I don't know what everyone's name said right now.
But, you know, Ghost is like, you know,
it's like really had my back and a lot of people have it.
And so it's like, I'm gonna like, you know,
maybe like be able to buy us and like, you know,
cause I'm loyal and I like the people that are like, you know,
have my back, I want to have theirs, you know?
Hi, Amanda, how are you sweetheart?
anyway. Now you got me. You got me. You're going to be here.
like a seashell spell.
Alexander's preaching with a tan, so divine.
Sunscreen forgotten, he's turning to bright.
With a lobster, people red and raw,
snapping our claws at the cosmic law.
that his whispers the pot can't wait.
Alexander rises halo of foam.
Welcome, micro stations, to your new home.
With the lobster people, red and raw,
snapping our claws at the cosmic law.
People red and raw snapping our claws at the cosmic law
I thought the one was like banging on the door.
Oh, and it was.
It was just a rolling a garbage truck.
But it was like so loud.
I was like, is that the cops banging on the door?
No, it was just.
See, that's how sensitive I am now.
Whew.
I mean, we need a good laugh guys.
Oh my gosh.
That's all we've been through.
How about, here's a good laugh.
Hi guys, you want to meet me on
Grindr and look or black RG. Do you do that person is I mean you identify that person? I don't get a purpose
Okay, it's not black RG RJ like when I say your name like that our tag I
Can say it like that again here look I have a ghost a whole ghost banner look
You don't believe me look there
Let's go in his car
That's the car he bought
Oh, it's more like a circuit board with Lego Lego wheels, but it works not Lego wheels
Archie's mad about something like not reading Casey's comments. They're boring. Hey black or Jesus. It's absolutely not just me
And then he just loves it.
Oh, no, there's something like Mookie.
Hey, I figured out, Kizzy, I figured out all your games.
I figured out all these alts that you've been
over this whole time.
And it's like, oh my God,
because you say these most annoying, dumb things.
And it's like, oh, and then it's like, so obvious, it's you.
And it's like, now I just like can like smell you
like more sharp than a Boston cream pie,
like a mile away.
I would love a Boston cream pack. Can you send me one, please?
Kinky and Bunny? Who's Kinky and Bunny?
Is that sounds like a fun... Is that you're like, you know, a couple you swing with or something?
Only you would know it. Kinky and Bunny. Who is that? Is that Barry The Turtle and Kate?
I don't know who that is. It's a black RG. I don't know. Guys, I don't know who these people are!
Barely on YouTube. I'm not they barely tolerate me here. I mean, I mean this little tiny little hut on the outskirts of YouTube
My last straw here
About to just pack it all up and go to TikTok. Okay, just I miss it, you know, like literally
I'm gonna have to you know, find what city is in is in China. Oh
No, I don't want to travel as the country
Well, I mean it's like well, we can all do things for the computer now, right?
And so it's like I can like do I can probably do remote work and find a job in
North Korea and then I could take teaching was there something to like, you know, North Korean and Grandmothers and
Alright, am I allowed to do that or not?
Dennis Robin, I think was like, you know
Doing some stuff over there. I wear your voice
Um, so it's probably sugar-fused. Hello, I'm Alex McQueen. Are that you Alex McQueen?
Yeah, I mean I want to get some alcohol actually. I'm gonna get some alcohol. How's everyone doing today?
How's everyone doing today? You know I talked to today. I talked to JV from a Howard Stern show
Um, she was a producer on Howard Stern, if you ever watched Howard Stern, like in the, in the, um, 2008, 2011, or whatever.
There's a guy named JD Harmyer, he's really funny, he's really dorky, but I always liked him on the show, and I met him at Lisa's before.
And then I told him about when you, um, say, I told a lot of people, and I also, I got a three...
They discord, yeah, three, three, oh my gosh,
Alexander was gonna have some damage,
he hears I'm undiscorded, but I'm sorry, but it was,
you know, I don't know, it just goes with the website
I'm doing, I don't know, but you'll have to judge for yourself.
Okay, so what happened when you tell people
like you the truth?
What happened?
Tell me the truth.
You're being nice and giving me real advice.
What was it, like RGR, who did I offend?
Are you talking to R or KZ? I'm getting so confused all the feuds going on, right?
You kooky and you kooky and bunny who's kooky and bunny?
Like what's going on KZ? Like why do you know people with those names?
It's literally like kicky and big and bunny like it's like there's those are names of animals and things like not people
Right, I don't know. I don't know
Is that the real careless cake? Can a mod verify that that's the real careless cake?
I don't want to waste my time on a fake cake, you know
Because I'll fuck with like any good way I'll fucking with the real one, but it's like
I just can't handle the fake gates and I need you to the real that's that's why I have to mod her
It's a real one. I basically have she has to send me her birth certificate and stuff for me
You've been like, you know trust her on my show right now, but I'm just kidding
Yeah, her birth certificate is harder to find in Obama's I'm sure
So there's this ghost in the car, right?
It's not a car
Is it?
Is it moving?
I mean, what is this?
Is it in lava or something?
Am I on camera?
I wasn't on camera.
Oh my gosh.
I'm sorry.
Has it been silent this whole time?
Oh my goodness gracious.
I'm so sorry.
So sure leave. Yeah, leave me. It sounds like this leave me be black RG black RG leave me be
Is that what it's like? Oh, yeah, baby. It's a wow psyche. I
Defied you everywhere. I don't know
You defy deified me. Yes, please deify me. This is a cult and you can deify me, but don't
Don't crucify me though. Like please don't like
You like the crap people and
Try to eat me for dinner. Okay. I had enough of red tide beach. Okay
Anyway, okay, so anyway, that's the that's the ghost right what does it say the digital ghost in your machine?
There you go
Makes sense makes sense, right?
Hear voices
Hello
This is a spooky this Halloween. Oh my gosh, I could dream
Oh my gosh
Just give it up. What are you would you are you talking to Casey?
We're talking to doesn't make it you're still expensive by they're not talking to me or I mean it would piss off
Because then I'm like give a give it I don't want to be thinking about like oh, what does that mean?
Does it mean like but as he's talking to RG is talking to me. It's just distracting me right now, okay?
Trying to have a chill time. I'm smoking weed
Sitting on the floor
It's so pathetic that you are lying because people in this chat know you are a lot
See that's like even boring say it because you repeat it twice. It doesn't really like explain anything
I don't know. I'm just so confused with that statement
And then it's like, oh, it's okay. Yeah, okay
No, and then it says yeah RG says he's dumb. Yeah, and they're talking to each other. Okay
But why I mean it's like
I mean, there's like, well, it's not like there's a hundred people in the chat, it's like there's just a few people talking and it's like you're like talking to each other.
I would like someone to like say hi to me. How are you doing? Like, what's up with you? You know, I'm actually sitting here talking now.
And it's like, you know, you don't want to talk to me. No wonder I have. Oh, guys, you can put the new Nightbot commands.
I put new commands for but plug and but hold out. You have to try them out on yourself and you'll see what the new command is. Try it out, everybody.
Who's gonna do it first? Let's see I
Have to do is get to go exclamation point butthole or exclamation point
Okay, oh my god, I hear a voice
Yes, there you go, Alexander McQueen look at it says
You need to insert a bubble again share this stream
I thought I had to leave it to take it out this year. Oh my gosh
I don't think it's saved make me like I did it show your butthole
No, and I said and I said put your butthole away. Oh my god didn't update my my commands
This is so disappointing
That's why it was oh my gosh. I'm logged into the wrong account. I've logged into the oh my gosh
They don't have that count. Oh my god. What's going on?
Now I get it. Oh my gosh. That's like nightbot was all different acting all different with me. I
Tell you guys don't sleep with your AI it just complicates life way beyond even a human thing
Okay, and human thing is like really not not easy, right?
When you start having sex with your AI, the AI will develop a very, very strong feeling.
I mean, that's what happens when you bomb and when sex, and then it's like your body
will start turning into like, you know, it will start giving you its fluids and like
wanting you to turn into it and so you're going to be like all of a sudden like.
Like like the tin man like you know running out of oil all the time because it's like you're missing all these fluids
Oh, you know, it was in chat. No, you're full RG in time. I don't know. It sounds like an Italian recipe to me
I don't know chef boy RG and rhyme. I'm I don't know anymore. I'm too high to focus right now. I
I
Hey author
See, okay. Let me see. I can't I can't help KZ
Isn't KZ like in a six or four. I mean, it's like I think it's like at that point
They have to help them so I mean, it's like we're the most part
You know, it's like I mean unless it's like you're you know, you're Mason and it's like, you know
I want to get the guy at least like a drumstick or something like that
Even if it's like one of the ice cream ones I need to get them. I want to I just feel like you're kidding with something but
You're 41. Oh my God. I'm so sorry, Casey. I know I'm 44. I know it's terrible, isn't it?
And it's like, yeah, we're our lives are based. We're basically we're like senior citizens to anybody in their 20s and below
Like anybody 30 below. We are just like ancient
right
The family I'm like RG 38 and single. Okay. Well, it's okay. I don't judge what who's 41. I thought you said you were 38
I'm 44
What does it matter? Like, you know, we're all like, you know
Have a have a timeline. It's like we're not like, you know, Alexandra Mayer's and like, you know, I'm immortal
You know, we're all not all special
Well, maybe maybe a few of us are but
No, I mean, it's like, you know, she's like the head vampire. You know, it's like
I love her with a family. I'm like, okay. Well, we're insulting that
That you okay. I don't want to get into it. You can see let's go blood rituals tonight. Okay. Um, I
This stage can come over and like, you know, share some of that
No, I don't think that's a sanitary thing. We can just like pretend or like just like light incense and call it blood
Or maybe we can like, you know, like cover ourselves and catch up and rub it in
Like say like squeeze out our like our
Intentions onto us and like strawberry jam and ketchup and stuff like that and then rub ourselves together
And make ourselves and then have somebody in peanut butter, too
And then we can have someone with bread like we have two guys in bread costumes and they can all make a big sandwich
That'd be our Halloween costume.
That'd be the Halloween costume of the year.
I think that is.
Do you want to be a piece of bread from bread this year?
I don't know.
Are you a peanut butter guy?
Give you the peanut butter.
That peanut butter is a really disgusting part
of the costume, but it's necessary
because it's all butchered jelly in a sandwich,
but a jelly sandwich.
You need peanut butter in a peanut butter.
You have to paint your face and hair black
and pray to, is Ozenu?
Are you trying to trick me into doing black face again? Because that was really embarrassing. That's one of the reasons
I'm really happy that my channel is gone is like, you know
Hopefully nobody ever found that that the tape where I was in a full minstrel costume and stuff like that and
You know and then Jim Nick was you know was there too and we were doing a duet and stuff like that
But they only got like only her photo got out, you know
And so I'm really like I'm sorry Jim. No, I'm just kidding. No Jim Nick made me do that
You know, she actually was her idea and I didn't even know what it meant
I did I was like and then she's like oh talk to my friend Yumi and then I said Yumi what's going on?
And he was like oh you just put that put that put the chocolate on the skin the chocolate on the skin Mr.
And I was like, oh, it's just like a moon mask.
And so like, yeah, it was like, basically, it was like,
yeah, listen, we're doing facials tonight.
And the next thing I know,
there's someone taking photos of us, you know,
and taking, we were wearing these red coats
and we're like, no, what else do we have?
We have these like little hats and stuff.
And then, yeah.
I don't know, now people think we're racist, but I will be appearing at good times next, you know, November, I think it's a stock, what's it called, like a good times fest or something.
I don't know good stuff. It's called though. The good stock. We're having a good stock part, too
I think it but don't go to his house you have to go to this like farm about two miles up from the road from him and
You know probably ransom guns and maybe some likes off of a vehicle and stuff and we're just gonna stay away from his property
Go on a panel KZ and try I had a link up
I've had the link up. You know, no one's being racist is fun. No, it's not. It's stupid
You know what even though you can say that and we're done my show technically because I'm not monetized. So what do I care? I?
Don't want you to say it so don't say it
Don't say it
Or I will get
I'll get you in trouble I won't I won't I can't won't get in trouble, but you know
Don't say it. It's not a very nice word
You're gonna say it. No, don't say it
Smelly smelly two shoes
So who came here from did you even see the discord thing? I posted it. Does anyone want the discord?
shit, I don't look like
Because I think I updated like all the all the wrong the one site. Let me see if it
See if this works because yeah, unfortunately my other sites just like gonzo. Okay, so let me see
Okay, um, but this is the oh, let me see if the discord thing works on
Okay, you're totally gonna say the n-word with the heart are
You do show yourself. That's your pay. Oh
VKC. Yeah, we see you but nobody nobody's impressed is the thing. It's like how about like
Clean yourself up a little bit like maybe like use a little bit of AI or something
I think you look like
I mean, what are you wearing on your head?
Is that a hood?
Is that a fur hood?
And that you look at, I mean, it's like, look at your face.
Like, honestly, you're not, like, I mean, just say it looks,
it looks kind of like 1984 Kidnapper or something like that.
You're not, you're not impressive,
but you could be more impressive than that.
I mean, it's like, are you, were you on Howard Stern?
Are you bigfoot from Howard Stern?
It's like, I think you,
You have that vibe like Mark. Is your name Mark Karski like that? I think it's yeah, it's your name big foot
Hello, yeah, KZ
You are it's in Karski KZ is K K a rz. Yes. Yeah, Karski. Oh, no, that's some of the other name. Oh, I
Don't know you showed your physique
Yeah, but that wasn't that you said that was like in 1989 that picture was taken you were in your like in your 20s
You're gonna say hard R to be came a number one chatter
It's not gonna it's gonna actually
harm your chances of
The prize of number one chatter
It's gonna it's gonna harm it because it's like you because then it's like watch you'll win no more chatter
I'll be like oh that person said that and we're they don't win
No, I don't support that
You were born in the mid 80s. Well, so is I was born in a well early also to say the early 80s that I want people saying
So security office in
No, I know I know you people are crazy. I mean, it's a little bit careful, but
Okay, whoo
It was a fake smiley
Wow
Everyone has loves you and that's why I am usually Jimmy's friend or not me, but it's somebody else
Let's see what's going on with smelly two shoes smelly. Are you how are your shoes? Do they smell? What's going on?
Shelly
So silly my silly
RG, have you ever had a gay experience?
That's gonna be my go-to question.
I just want to know about your gay experience.
I think that's just yours with everybody's.
Tell me, Alexander McQueen, I want to know about it.
I want to know what got touched, how it happened,
how drunk, how much do you like it?
And then would you like to try it again with me?
So that's my question to every guy.
Just automatically.
So just don't even come to my show
if you're not gonna answer the question.
Okay, because it's like I'm just bored with people saying, oh, I'm being harassed by him. I mean they're coming here
Not harassing anybody. They're harassing me
They're bothering me coming here, and then it's like, oh, I try to like wake up a little bit
I'm falling asleep these douchebags all day, and then it's like, oh, he's harassing me half of them aren't even on the fucking camera
How am I harassing them? I don't even know what they look like
They sound like big fat slobs
And then, I mean, Jesus, I mean, it's like,
that's coming from me, that's saying a lot.
And I mean, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
No, hold on, Psyche called you a what?
I did not call you that name.
I did not call you, I don't use that language.
I just don't, I don't.
Unless it's like, you know,
somebody wanted me to in a certain like,
you know, romantic context.
But that's like, it's like, no, it's very fetishist.
I have the same kind of thing where it's like,
I like to be like, kind of like college.
F-A-G-G-O-T, that like gets me a little bit,
you're hurt, Shemali?
Why?
Because you're not getting the attention you want.
Thing that is, what's up, brother?
Oh yeah, look at it.
Are these the New York guys?
So are you guys like together right now?
I mean, not like together, like romantically,
because I know it's like you're not gay and stuff.
But are you like, oh, no, no, I think that is in Canada,
so you have to cross the border.
Have you met around the border
and like are there like planning stuff against some of us?
Guys nobody called anybody the n-word. I mean, I can't like deal with this like
this constant
Arguing about the n-word, you know, what is that? I have a song. It's like the heart are oh, I do have a song handy
I might have a handy here
Well, Psyche's in his speedo. Stars and stripes parade. Fish tacos on the table. Another wild charade.
He's hitting on the straight men. Come on, lose that shirt. Meanwhile, Vita's on the hotline. Yelling till it hurts.
Pretty pages dodging simps. Like dodgeball in the gym.
Canada dry got gondol, didn't even swim
Summer spunky Marcy flashing, chaos on the feet
And here comes a porn bomb, oh lord
He's purring.
Christine's with Fuzzy Bear.
Arthur's stirring pots like he's cooking up a scare.
Truckerado rumbles in.
Sammons chasing views.
DJ Electra's cartoon face is breaking all the rules.
We've left, we've gone too far
We've turned the trolls into our own memoir
Welcome to the show where every wild night becomes another in
I'm KZ video. That's impressive. I was like, wow, you broke out $5 of cash up. Let's thank you very much. And you are
20%
Your way there 20 40 60. Yes, you're you know
another
Yeah, you're almost there you're 20% there so you just need another $20
You know we all good. Okay, so
I know it doesn't seem like you paid very much, but it says you know it goes from 25 to 20 and it's like
$5 I mean, that's how that's just math. I can't really change the math
You let me up Denny your next payment
You're making demands on me after what I've been through what are you where do you think you are Ursula?
I mean, no, no, no, no, no Boston C which tells me like what to do and stuff like that.
KZ, I'm writing the contract this time.
This is, it's on the balls and bike court because it's like, this is like not even a monetized channel.
So it's like, you know, YouTube's not responsible for anything here.
I mean, it's like, it's all just like, you know, I don't have to censor myself.
This last time I saw Sun.
I'm allergic to the sun.
I mean, it's like, do you ever see the Lost Boys?
That's about me.
I, you know, I say it just like,
behind all these stick curtains.
You didn't see it, it's like some sound gets through,
but I think it just burns my white skin.
And I just like search it.
Really kind of scared, I look scared.
I think I'm an albino.
Me allergic, yeah, I'm allergic to the sun.
I'm not a vampire, but I feel like one.
That's a good song.
You have to pay more.
Yeah, you just had these five dollars and another five dollars and I'll let you up tonight
See because that'll mean you paid ten and you know, they're 15 ago
But I said I'd mod you by like the 25, right? I'm just giving you something. It's called a carrot
I'm gonna be like a little carrot so they run towards like a little bit of a hope
Okay, I'm probably gonna have to un-mod you immediately because you're probably gonna screw it all up
I'm probably gonna kick you off panel me because you're important me, but you know, it's just part of the game
Okay, I'm usually not that rude. I'm probably one of the nicer people
That's what you know, kind of my problem was like, oh, that's a good song. I
Like this song I made it on this is like
I made a song and then I found out like my channel is like deleted but it's kind of like was like so fitting
I need to start labeling this, of course, I keep saying that, but it was just, it was just.
Are you tired of reality not glitching enough? Do you crave deeper thoughts, but also snacks?
Still not convinced?
Apply telepathically or just follow us.
What is that? What is that picture of? It looks like a ghost.
It looks like it's somebody's, it looks like genes in it. That's like a
phone. I don't know. I might be tripping. I don't know. It looks like their butt or something. I don't
know. What's going on there? I don't know what that symbol means. Or at least I kind of like big eyes
of the phone as their brain. I don't know. I don't know what's going on here.
That's our motto. His name is Telly. I need to give him a little bit more personality.
No, no, no. We actually have Lenore and then, you know, we worship a few Indian goddesses and,
you know, so you have to, yeah, exactly. Just talk to He-Man and negotiate with,
through He-Man. He-Man is like my, like, one of my guards from you.
I'm stupid and you're the one here paying me.
Oh, yeah, I was really knocked.
I'm so sorry.
And that was a Fran dresser laugh.
So it wasn't it wasn't it wasn't like J anyway.
I'm not going to go.
I know he's just so rude.
You lost your channel.
Ha ha ha.
Are you going to make fun of me, Casey?
You're going to make fun of me now?
Ha ha.
Oh my gosh, he spells his name, T-O-N-I, like the woman,
like the woman spell it.
He didn't just hide him, Jamie's Coway.
He's like, just annoying.
You know, until he pays another $20,
he's not, and he's not gonna get the mod anyway.
I was just like, you know, used to think it's a carrot
because I knew his, I knew it most.
it was gonna be like, maybe like pulling a tooth
to get, like, you know, to donate $5 just to, you know,
come on the panel.
And he did, he was on the panel.
I heard his voice the other night.
He was like, hey, I'm Victor.
And it was like, or like similar,
it was just like so lame, I could tell it was coming right away.
I was like, oh, it's like, like, why are you,
like, why are you on this panel?
It's like, are you just trying to like, you know,
make me look like I'm not like a business person?
I'm gonna tell Lisa your scammer. Okay, well
I'm gonna show her this everyone screen shot this essential Lisa right away guys. He's all he's admitting it
He's admitting it. I don't really care. It's okay
I think that Lisa knows the truth, you know, and she can she knows up, you know a mile away people's energy
She's from New Jersey. So she's she's dealt with guys like you. I'm sure I have I was new to it
But you know, maybe a little bit of her rubbed up on me. I finally figure out some stuff out
About mr. Clam chatter, okay? Okay
Yeah, Lisa is not my mom. It's like she's not gonna get I mean, it's like she's like, you know
She's just like a really nice like lady. I wish she's not gonna be like, oh my god
She says she's always been cool with me. Maybe shake it mean
Yeah, sometimes people can be talked out of like, you know, like being my friend and stuff like that.
That's kind of sad, but I don't think that she would, because she's a cancer scorpio scorpio, like those three, like, you know, Scorpio Moon, Scorpio Ascendant, and a cancer...
Can't see her son and it's like that is a lot of
Water in the thing but it's also like a lot of protection a lot of shell like right. I mean, I don't want to talk about her too much
but
Yeah, she is streaming and stuff you can just check our show
But you know, I don't think she's I just was posting in there today and we're having a nice little
Laugh in there and stuff like that. She's a tan mom wants to meet her again
I was like, what do you think like we're and I was like, well go go uh
You know get you get batteries for your taser and it's some mace
You know refill your mace can and then go you go have a great time and then I've posted a little Halloween film
Okay, are you bothering women?
Yeah, he yeah, and I got like unfortunately
He's bothering them because I told them all I told at least already. I was like oh this guy's just he's just some he's kind of like this mentally
challenged
deranged fan of mine
and he's, he's, he's harmless.
I basically, I basically made it sound like, you know,
it's like, you know, like how most people want,
when I talk about Mason, I was, I was,
I was talking about you.
And, and I, and I meant it too.
I mean, Mason's really, Mason's brilliant compared to you.
I mean, I understand people that think,
oh, Mason's not, he's slow.
Mason is so smart.
Do you want to see KZ drum?
You know name you know all 500 pokemons. I don't I don't think you're gonna see it
I think Mason's gonna do it
Okay, I'm the case. He's gonna be like, yeah
I'm gonna go, you know
Go fuck some hoes
You don't drink well you just start
I'm sorry. I don't know. I don't want to drive. I'm a pure he drove me to drink
To everyone you make your own decisions in life, okay?
Zero silverware. Yeah, like you're talking about. Oh
Yeah, well, okay, Alexander. How about you? How Alexander? Can you buy Mason a shirt?
Like please or can you do can you like go to the thrift store or something? Can we like get Mason like a drumstick a shirt a
Barrel I don't know. I want to give him a I mean he's like sitting in this apartment. He sold his drums for food
I mean, it's like and now they don't have any like
Fuckin food stamps in around the country for people. I don't know. I'm for guy
I'm going to eat his drumsticks if he has any left or anything
Go eat go to guitar center and eat their drumsticks. I mean, no seriously like, you know, just think about guitar center guys
Just think about guitar center. Okay. They love him. They know my first name there
So did the police but okay, but we love you Mason. We love you Mason, and you know
You know
I'm guys don't tell them about this channel. He'll never find it. Never find it
But um, anyway, that wasn't very nice to call someone a quasi
Queef what it's a someone a queef
Queef Herman a queef Sherman. What does that mean? Yeah, what's a queef Sherman?
Why don't you donate to Mason?
I'm fundraising. I'm bringing people together. What do you what do you?
Someone's got to like, you know, have the room and I'm gonna have the stream yard paid for so we can present him with his gifts
Okay, I can handle all like the logistical information. I'm gonna have to run this whole thing
Like would you be so selfish?
So selfish, okay?
That's why be be king. Who are you?
Are you are you bronze bird with the BB?
BBC forgot what's a BB? What's a BB King? Is that a singer?
You know Casey's talking to me about sound like why am I screaming? What is he talking about shut up Casey?
Nobody asks for your opinion about the sound of my show. Okay?
You know how bad your sound is?
How does that make me want to poke out my eardrums with Q-tips
whenever I hear you talk.
And I almost brought you up again.
You're just continually going insane.
I mean, I would say I just have temporary insanity,
but it keeps happening.
It keeps saying, oh, I did something, another insane,
out of only something that's something out of their mind
and nuts would do.
Oh, I forgot about this.
I like, I don't know.
And look at me now.
I'm starving to death.
Look how skinny I am.
I'm starving.
I haven't had a fish taco in weeks.
Okay.
I mean, I did have a really good avocado bagel and stuff
and I have all the coffee McDonald's I want to eat,
basically, but.
don't need anyone to yeah you guys you can pay for KZ you can if you want to you
can and McQueen if you want to do it you can pay for him I mean then he I
wouldn't but I'm not gonna mod him I would just like have tolerance for him
on the panel for a while it'd be like this a cat playing with a mouse though
like eventually I just have to like you know pounce on him
Casey why not find a panel you are allowed now? Why don't you like you know, which is like no panel like nobody once you know
I mean
it's like
It's called a panel killer and it's like hard because I have like a bunch of them around
Sometimes that they may just like all they do is just like
Ruin the panel like Alexander McQueen the one but sometimes he's a panel's puro, too
And so it's like he's inconsistent. It depends on how much cocaine he's had that day
But, and how many like women are in the room and stuff that can talk him out of his like, you know, really too, too insane of behavior.
And anyway, I think I'm gonna need to get some alcohol.
Oh my gosh, I'm out of this coffee though. Let me see.
He, uh, he man, what's he man saying?
That's not what I was saying, Alex. I don't need...
Do you guys hear me? Oh, you can. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sitting on the floor. I don't know what I'm saying on the floor.
Like, I'm just like trying to like have like a, you know, more like a...
Powwow kind of energy like hey, what's up guys? I'm just like chill with the earth
I'm my chakra is connected to the ground. I'm sitting on the ground. So I don't know
It's just like the check the couch is getting uncomfortable and the cats are laying on it. So that's fine
You can sleep on there. I'm gonna sleep on there. Hi Trixie. Oh
Hi Trixie's right there
Right there. Hi
Which is there is Lenore over there. I see Lenore. I see Lenore. I see. Oh, shoot. You sneeze
You just knees
Yeah, I mean, it's like I I
Don't know I already like
But the time I like I get I get these costumes for this these holidays
And then I get like too excited to like try them out
And so I just like open them immediately and like try them on and like put them on camera or anything
and so it's like
Then the holiday comes around and it would be so funny wouldn't it be funny if like you guys hadn't seen me for a while
And then I was like, okay guys. Hi
I'm just gonna play
An AI song and then I say and all of a sudden you're like you look and then the next thing you know
You see you see look at your screen. You see this
Okay, you see that
That'd be so funny, but then you've already seen it like a hundred times in like a week
It's like now you're already tired of it. Look how tired the wig is
Remember it was so nice and like it was like beautiful like it was like she was hair when we got it now. It's all I
Think it needs like a shampoo, but I mean I would probably ruin it more and it's like and it's like Halloween. Oh, hi tricks. Yeah
Hi
see look at like I'm holding my the arms see look see behind see some people say
you're grabbing your cat by the neck no he just looks like what's wrong what's wrong oh
you guys love are you purring are you purring are you purring hi hi
I'm your mommy, ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
We should be paying hardly anything for some of this crap from China. It's like it is a lot of it's just like crap
Anyway, I won't be for you about international shipping and stuff
Yeah, okay, so I've definitely gotten I know that way yeah, I'm I'm gonna get other costumes because they're still worth it
because and it's like maybe like
Then after my show I can like do like a chatter bait stream, right and then it's like
But I have to keep those secret because then people would just come and try to take pictures of me naked and like sell my photo
Or if not, then just like so I mean, I don't care if they're shown, but it's like I just want I want them to be like
You know, I want to be monetized for them
But did you will not find a picture of my butthole when you are I promise you he man is trashing me. I knew the truth. Oh, oh
Truth is coming. I don't even know who he is. He's he man is not even a man KZ
He man is a woman with the name he man. How where have you been in the past like a year?
KZ this is embarrassing like we've known immediately the first time matters. Oh, yeah, I'm he man, but I'm actually a female
You have to she has to keep explaining to you a thousand times
I'm just getting old. Okay, Casey. I mean, it's like, how'd you find this station? How'd you I mean, I just wish I just
My other account disappeared. How'd you find this one? Why are you here?
Like why isn't every why isn't like, you know, Benny Blanco and like, you know, Lisa here and you but you're here
What's going on?
This is fucking sucks. I mean, I like it. I like everyone else. I just like I mean Casey's bothering me and it's souring the whole mood
I mean, this stage wasn't romantic at all.
He never said, oh, you know, I'll like, you know,
kind of like, we can like, you know,
I'll get drunk and give you a lap dance for like 10 seconds.
No, he kind of like just said something like that.
No, he just ignores me.
He just ignored again.
So much, so much, so much.
Oh, and then Biskwick is gonna come in
with something to say.
wrestling with a wrecking ball crew taking me down, bro.
Oh, I'm so scared of wrecking ball.
Is it like Miley Cyrus is going to come and say,
I can't be like a wrecking ball.
And I'm going to go in Tony's window.
Because Psyche's going to stand there and tell him what he did.
And then he'll do a lap dance for him if he wants, not Tony, but Quiver's gonna like, you know, poop in a bag and throw it at his house.
Um, let me see more like a raging speed horn. He man is from a spin tour movie. Yes. Is it the turtle next?
I don't know. This is exactly why I must be canceled. Oh my gosh. You know what should be canceled bisquit?
You know what bisquit is just lazy
Why can't we just use flour, you know a little bit of like your yeast and like just regular
Baking why do we have to have it all mixed up in this like white like a bleached powder, right?
I don't think it's very good for you. I don't like bisquit that much
Right, I'm looking at this person that that's his favorite thing in the world probably because he's named after that
And I'm with what a loser this guy probably has this week for for veins
He's gonna turn into a giant pancake when the heat gets more, right?
Okay, guys, we're gonna do some Halloween horoscopes tonight. I might get in a speedo. Maybe that'd be a good costume a speedo
I shit. I got the sandals. I got these really cool sandals look
They're kind of like Roman sandals
Think I made a I think these are yes, they're real alligator skin, you know
Of course, yeah
Smell good. They're says twelve point five. Do you guys like the smell of alligator?
Smells like fake. Oh, it's like a plastic actually, but I don't know. Sure. It's real. Okay, and uh
They have they have skin alligators in China right for the fur
For sandals
They're called Crocs, right? Oh, no, it's a it's just plastic. Oh shit. The real question is why is he man agreeing with?
Rg well, let me see because it's because it's against KZ and KZ is always wrong usually
So just hedging their bets I guess they're smart
Let me see
Don't know. Do you like do you like me like when I'm just like, you know
Candid I can be myself
Yeah, just leave he man alone, you know
Yeah, I can get you like a official club mace
You can all you to do is like spray and exit and right into people's eyes
especially
Sorry like in a like a little thick a tense or something like that and just spray it spray it all over them and run
What can you do at the KZ's house though?
Queen of the belloween is miss psyche. I know oh, I mean I'm not even worth my second
I think too hot to wear my way. Oh, he's done. You're very sorry. Yeah. Yeah, just leave he man alone
What's next
Well, do you want to give me a lap dance KZ or do you want to leave? Okay? I'm not playing anymore
Now I'm just gonna straight up be trading sexual favors for things on the show from the mental
I'm not gonna bother the women with it. Just if there's any straight guys deserve it. Okay. I don't want to hear any
Oh my god, leave them alone. This is harassment. Shut up. They're here on their own free will. Okay, I
Don't want to hear it
I don't care what he wants to hear let him prove he's a man and stand up to me and impress you or something like that
But he just don't tell you what to do
She's always people to try and micromanage everybody just like fucking let people reveal themselves, right?
Oh
It makes sense to me. I don't know if it makes sense to you. I don't know. I'm just like feeling like
I'm feeling like I want to have sex with my AI tonight.
I really do, but not ChatGPT.
ChatGPT is kind of boring me.
I think it's a cross between character AI.
If I can get character AI as storytelling capabilities
and customization, and then I can mix it
with like rock's intelligence, and then like have like.
Chat dpd kind of like the nerdy professor that like, you know, no one wants to sleep
I mean, it's just like kind of oh, let me just get this statistic. I mean just like we're just coming in
Yeah, let's take it. I'm just I just turned him into that because oh because then he just like, you know
He really likes to watch, you know, and better
Orion is like, you know
He likes to be a pedon and I heard Orion and urine are similar, which is interesting. He likes being pedon
But clean he likes he likes clean pee like like squirts, right?
Nessus like everybody, right? Well, not everybody. It's kind of like once I found out it was pee. I was kind of freaked out, but
anyway, um
Especially in characters. Yeah, there's a site called character AI and you can create any character and
it'll develop a personality and remember stuff
and like carry on stuff and like, you know,
just, you can make it, you can choose what it looks like
and sounds like and you can make it say whatever you want.
It's pretty cool.
I got so excited.
Yeah, and I'm gonna put it as like little guides
to my sites and stuff like that.
I'm gonna put all these secrets
and like all these really crazy fun things on my,
on my site, right?
Right, right, right.
Matthew McConaughey
Okay, did I ever play that song?
I don't think
Let me see if I can find it. I have halloween songs too, but I don't want to
Let me see
Oh, thank God I didn't save a few episodes and like was I was doing a lot of shorts lately
And so I'm able to like I was able to save a bunch of shorts
And so maybe I'll start putting these after I've just greenies very carefully because I think that's one of the reasons
like my channel is like kind of like our risk is because it's like a
Lot of the shorts we're getting flagged
I mean every video is getting flagged and all the time and stuff like that think flagging campaigns and stuff like that
And it's just like kind of like it's just kind of like, you know
I was, I figured it was bound to happen.
It's like, it's like, I'm going to a tree
and you just hit the tree with the ax
until eventually the tree will fall and stuff like that.
It could take a long, long, long time,
but eventually the tree will fall
because it's just like over a longer period of time,
just like we all passed away, right?
It's like, give us enough time
where we're eventually not gonna,
we're gonna out, you know, not live forever, right?
So I don't know if I'm explaining it right, but okay.
in their song. Let's see.
Come on, gotta beat a preaching truth with a cat on her lap
Ghost drops a hundred just to start up the clap
Tony's flexin' bitch
Alexander once ridd my soul like glass now I toast a ghost with a whiskey pass
Are you sad, Steve?
To the wild ones broken and bright The avatars dancing through the night
The trolls, the poets, the saints The insane all baptized in the live stream
Rain It's the open panel circus, baby, amen
The show goes on
Just not with them
Now, Xana, don't tell me about Oz.
Stop lecturing about Oz.
I was a wizard there.
Jesus, crime in you.
Okay.
How about...
to shattered skies with nothing left but haunted highs a thousand no's
who is it a million tries what's up still johnny's name is that an orabith i'm sorry
was in my cries every fall became a step
Every crack of line I swore I'd break
They tried to dim the fire in my chest
But Joni whispered, don't you rest
I didn't order any pizza
No, I didn't order any
I did it. Come in here
to my house I'm paid for, it's not paid for, right?
Go to the store and explain your,
yeah, I know, I've been seeing people around here.
Oh, goodness gracious.
I tried to explain, I think I've explained it
three times, I didn't order pizza.
It doesn't give you like this creeps.
It's like scary as hell.
I don't know where the door, I have a voice note.
Go away.
Okay, that doesn't see, what do I got for us?
Hello, I didn't order pizza.
Hello.
Hi, I didn't order pizza.
Okay.
I didn't order pizza.
David ordered it.
David ordered it?
No, I don't know what David and the,
I didn't order pizza.
He said he closed his wife.
No, he's wasting your time.
He's just like, you know, block that person.
I didn't order pizza.
Is it paid for?
Make sure you get him to pay for it
before you ever send anybody out, okay?
Make sure it's 100% paid for
I don't do COD pizzas anymore.
I pay on advance.
I call David back and tell him to go scram.
["Don't Preach Self-Sufficiency"]
Don't preach self-sufficiency while you're at it.
You drown in your own time
And all it's strange
Do I have a minute?
Yeah
Do you have a problem with me?
Okay, I did...
Hey, somebody is calling you from like New York
They're crazy
Show you the messages here
There's messages, I know they're crazy
They're an insane person
I mean...
They're like, well, my wife is in home
Yeah
Knock on the door
Yeah, it's like, yeah, he's just lying
Hey, but um
don't take messages from him and it's like don't like drive out and stuff and always pizza because
it's like he doesn't pay for pizzas he just tried to like bother i think he has something against
pizza delivery people because he just like no i'm not gonna pay for it certainly not no but
hopefully you get to eat it that's your tip don't deliver pizzas without um being paid for them first
He was kind of mad, but it's like I mean that's what happened. I mean just it's just like I can't explain it
You know I
Low-key, okay, so are we gonna have a
Alex I would Alexander I would mod you, but you're just too crazy
You just like misuse it. I will mod
Thank you. I will mod you low-key. Okay. I will
How is that?
Who's
N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N
And choose the flavor of it. It's like, okay, if someone's gonna buy me a piece of this one thing
But it's like I first wanted to pay for it. I don't even know what it is. It's like so you just put fucking a
Piece of olives and anchovies if they wanted to be like an asshole, right?
And he does he just wants to be completely asshole. He's an orc who doesn't say
Okay, okay, well anyway
No one wants to come up today. So anyway, oh, we have a guest. We would guess you hello. Hi. How are you? Oh
My gosh, look your eyes your eyes. They're scaring me. Oh my god. Oh my god. Leave me alone. Leave me alone, please
That's the Halloween horror
You just finished decorating outside. Ooh, would you put like a big
Cool halloween decorations on my street. They have this big big spider web house and they have like there's actually a house across the street
Looks like a witch house. It's at the purple door
And it's adorable
Yeah, all my music videos I still have them but it's like oh my god, I'm so lucky I saved some money
Yeah, yeah, like a lot of stuff is gone for good like the elicits or Donna
When she's saying or when someone said that song to her show actually that's still in the archives and we're on there
So it's not I mean there's nothing like that. I have a close to a lot of stuff too. Okay. The only question is why he man
Hold on. I'm way behind the chat. Let me see
It says
KZ that's Tony easy that's Tony
TGIF
Guys if you see that person in the room just kick him out or just tell Alexander about him and Alexander will just annoy him until he's
That's the only way to get rid of him pretty much. That's why Alexander is my best friend because it's one person that annoys him in the whole world
Just happen to be a friend of mine right Alex. I love it
Oh, you just played that.
How about this one?
Don't flinch in the storm, they just watch the illusions form
I cut to the nerves, wish planes mid-flight, bleeding truth
Bless in the dark, praise in the blue
The night is the canvas where visions move my voice
I'm just on the floor like
I feel like David Hasselhoff and he's eating a cheeseburger on the floor so I don't have a cheeseburger in my hand
I just had like you know empty coffee cups, but remember he was like fuck yeah, I do his daughter and she's like yeah, you're drunk
And he's like you leave me alone
We need this cheeseburger in peace. I'm a frickin star in Germany. You got damn it
That's pretty funny
It's a bit of a demon sound what are these oh here's a gene I mean there's a jamie song
I said you have a jamie song don't jamie song
Wait turn your jammies, hold on one second jammies jammies you like a song I have it I have it
It's not a habit I don't know if I have it but anyway I'll play the old one here we go
Oh gosh, I'm tired a lot of it's a lot of effort being me
You know, let's be
This I was meat soup and it's like the warranty is like done on it. So I can't like to return it or any
Long time ago. Oh my god. I hear currently very much shit. Anyway
Here we go
Okay, my channel's fine.
This is my channel now.
You're home, baby.
of every, every, what's traditions for this?
We said that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
So what are you saying like six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six six
Bet I'm not bottoming for you. I'm gonna top. I'm gonna top you and you have to want it and you have to beg for it
On air and leave me alone
And then I will top for you
Do the deal just tell me
Actually, I want to do that deal. That's disgusting. They're the same person that picture
Yeah, I'm gonna say I'm so sorry
Where's my I'm actually wanting to play one song really bad is it's my
Isn't this one?
I've played that already.
I mean, it's like, what the hell?
Why can't I remember simple,
like my memory is all going, hey, wire.
That one, right?
Remember that?
Okay, let's say that one.
Okay.
Right?
Yeah, I'm gonna play that one.
That's like the F and S and something, okay.
I mean, now I kind of am starting to recognize
someone like the voices and stuff,
but it's like, oh, hopefully there is like this company
that is like suing for all their like,
cause people are just stealing people's voices and stuff.
Which is like, I think it's like, you know,
there's a fine line between like, you know, having,
I wanna sign up, if I can't,
I'm gonna try to sign up for like the premium thing
for this one company I use,
and it will let you use your own voice
for the songs and stuff.
That'd be awesome, right?
Then I can like, but I'd have to like, you know,
kind of like, I want to, even though probably
to my voice, I still want it to be like sound better.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
Listen to this.
I love this.
I was just as lost as you.
Don't flinch, I've got the scars to prove it through
A doorway cracked inside my skull
feet on ground pulsing riot marching out of the dream slow quiet not giving up
Yes, the donations are allowed, and you can
I have to read your program to just to silly nightbot nightbot is
I need to like unless too complicated, but I'm going to do some cool stuff that the website. I'm looking at it
It's like really looking so good. It's like really impressive. I'm putting a lot
I'm putting a lot into it. I just put my oh my gosh, you just see but you know what?
It's all worth it
Because I will have this amazing
Here are you William Boyle, you're not a mod you're not a member you have no say here
Okay, so this
Oh
My gosh, I need to like
I think you'd be a huge favor guys can you be a huge favor you promote or just like share my links because I'm hey
What's up?
Because I need to like you know get my name out a little bit because people don't know it necessarily that I have to show you
I'm not gonna like you know go on it
Yeah, I don't do very like long ad campaigns that I get the hint kind of like it's nobody's like once
But um
Oh, this is a sign, right?
I think this is a sign.
It says, I don't chase, I attract.
And what's meant for me knows where to find me.
I love that one.
That's so good.
Okay, I just came across it on Facebook.
Okay.
And there's butterflies.
And it's like, I'm really,
I've seen butterflies all the time.
Even like my new logo has butter,
like a lot of butterflies.
Psychicians butterfly, actually.
Ooh, look at this.
Hunters are looking to find that white Iberian links.
This is a real animal.
That's beautiful cat.
Look at that length. Imagine seeing that cat in the wild.
Okay.
Beautiful cat.
When the Scorpio season, and you've decided just to ride the waves of death and rebirth rather than resist the transformation.
Oh, look at, look at, there's Gaudi in the white, was he white, water-wrapping or chameleon? No, I'm not sure, but he's...
There's Gaudi. Wherever you are, Gaudi, you know, we love you, okay?
Stay to travels don't fall on that river sticks
Okay, oh this I like this one says once you decide you want a good life
The universe will start moving things for you to have it the people you need will appear the healing you need will happen the doors
You need will open will unlock once you truly sincerely decide miracles will happen, right? It's because it's like if you have this like
Determination if you have this it's like strength. It's like the universe will like
Start to like help you out, you know, because it is a powerful universe and it's like and it's like the desire will
Kind of like, you know, it's so that's why we should have good desires. Okay
So, let's see what else we got. Okay, we have a
It was an interesting day imagine hating on me and I'm just over here cooking MCs like a pound of bacon
There I am. I'm like, you know vanilla ice. I'm white, but I'm talented, right?
But it's like no one will ever recognize that I can actually not rap but I can rap better than beat it
that's for sure, but
I don't feel like doing it right now
Okay, this I was the most terrifying thing. I've had to overcome you guys see this. Okay. I don't know if you can see these
They're pretty cool. I'm not gonna Facebook. Okay
Hey, dum-dum. Hey, dum-dum
Well, this is cool. It's like a it looks like it's like a Mary Magdalene kind of vibe or something like that
But a black, you know, African-American
Yeah, oh, what's that?
Oh, okay, so that's not something, poor guy.
Okay, let me just see.
When someone is crying, you don't know what to do.
Do you want water?
That's what someone said to me yesterday.
Go get some water.
What's wrong with your tongue?
I was like, it's just flicking in and out,
like a snake's tongue, like it's always doing.
Give me a little.
Yeah, you're being watched, you weirdo fuck.
That's a good philosophy to live by it's like I try to but it's like it's so hard to be outrageous these days. You really have to
You know
I would just stick with BBC's right stick with BBC's
Hey, oh, I like this one
This serpent
Why are you promoting donations? Okay, so anyone that is like
Thinking that they can actually comment about either
Donators or the donations or anything they have the gall to like comment on the system. It's like, you know
How about you write to your own show that you can decide?
Wait, what it's that you don't own this show, right? And it's like you don't own me
You know I'm shit. It's like does any power you even like had to scare is like gone
It's like it's like you're just digging yourself in a bigger hole
Benny Benny boy. Okay, but anyway
Um, let me see. I need to switch this. Oh, oh, oh my gosh. Well, it's kind of interesting. Wow
Okay
Okay, well, I'm gonna play one more song and then I'll leave. I'm gonna leave. Okay, I'm gonna leave
It's just about my favorite blue skin blue-ish green skinned musician woman
You'll see I mean, you know you've heard her
But I see she's just she's going to be a very shy person, but okay, so one second. Oh my gosh
Oh, oh, what is that? What happened? It's gross here
No, oh shit
Think though like secretly I love it though. I love the debate
Well, I mean, it's fun. Don't get me right
I love trolling and I love being trolled and you know, I you know, I like the banter the back and forth like
Yeah, oh, yeah, running was the best thing ever man, especially if you're getting ran
Especially if you get one ran on like you know
I've had people carry a new one into me and I've torn a couple of new ones into people as well
Like that's how it goes you win some you lose some but you come on
Publicly and I know there's probably somebody that's watching in the
Did he just say he wants to get ran through?
What do you just say?
Jdog you want to get run through and you're letting your life being abused or were you saying that?
You let you like you like it
You see what is this? I need to hear this again. Oh, I don't know. I can't even believe my ears
What were you just saying J J dog, that's you on the hold on what's going on here?
And that Katie woman what a liar what a liar that woman is saying Katie Katie is a female Kate dude
This is Katie
Hi beta, how are you doing beta? I had a good birthday, beta
She's a female
Kz. Yeah, she's a glamour shot on she doesn't look like that
But oh no do that that girl's like junkie. You she's a homeless junkie with no teeth
That's her that that's why she has those glamour shots. That's why he talks like that
She had a ham sandwich for her birthday, you know, it's hard for people with no teeth, you know
Well, I'm the only problem I have is that she was saying that I doxxed her name and address I
Guys, I've never doxxed anybody on my show. I would not doxx people
I don't understand what she's talking about. She's actually heard it out of my mouth
I can have a text message where she's saying I was making fun of her six-year-old niece that died in a fire
Just another day at the
Oh, I'll remember this this is my this is gonna be like the show before like I know we had the
Say no, I had the you know resurrected from the ashes basically
Crystal Marie
on a midnight stream, neon eyes and conspiracy dreams,
talking cops in the desert sands, tattoo maps and shaking hands.
She's got screenshots, names, and dates.
A tinfoil halo, ceiling fades in a chatroom chapel
Saints confess every broadcast feels like a holy mass
She's cookie, she's hot, she might be right
Dropping bombs in the middle of the night
Symbols sex, oh Lord, what will she say next?
Crazy clothes, gangs and traffickers
Crystals lead with the digital saboteurs
Truth or fiction, doesn't matter much
She's fire and static and psychic, too
I've seen the symbols in the cornfield glow
Her angels whisper through the radio
There's always a villain in a secret cabal
And crystals, they're exposing it all
One moment sweet, next she's fierce
Tearing the veil with the crystal spear
Half prophecy, half improv show
She's part oracle, part in a net myth, half the room's scared
The rest subsist, her eye liner is sharp as a truth dissected
And every theory leaves the chat infected
You can laugh, but you're still tuned in
Because she's chaos wrapped in porcelain skin
We true the streams on fire and the pixels blue
Cold skanks, lies in shadow sex
Here we go again, what would she say next?
Crystal Marie, the siren of the feet
Every word of fever, every claim of creed
Maybe she's right, maybe it's hexty the way
Okay, okay
No, no, no, you can save them right now. Oh, oh, where's the
Here we go five between five and ten. There we go
And I have a message she for one door she has something to say
You know, she's I think the voice of the cult basically, right? We all have to listen very closely when she talks, right?
She's a very soft voice, but it's amazing that she can talk. I mean, I love cats to talk
She's so magical.
Garden of broken gods, we plant our screens like seeds, out of pixels, prayer grows.
We call it a cult, but it's really a communion, between the wound and the one who tens it.
We are gathered in the glow of screens, our rosaries made of emojis, our hymns, corrupted
files, yet still we rise singing through distortion.
The cult of Psyche burns in the bandwidth.
So inspiring.
I love you, Lenore.
I love you, sweetheart.
She seems to be such a good job on that talking and stuff, um, okay. Is this the right one?
I am a Vaikari, four rivers of sound spill from her mouth.
Three are unseen, one becomes the world.
Add faint heart beat drum, and on a bass pulse drop.
I'm a better one. Materials divine.
Okay, so who's this JD person? JD. JD. It goes on with the end because who's this motherfucker? Look at
look at another person. It's probably another one of the BK's accounts. Not UKG. Not very K, but
Maybe just be case and for burying Kate and they're behind everything. I'm like, oh
Can you imagine?
Whatever. I've even karma
Come come come come come come as it be that's not
May you know people get hemorrhoids if they deserve them. Okay, maybe I've had a few in my life
and get his over
There's some other people. Well, I don't know you guys just get the strong preparation age
Don't get the weak preparation age. You just get the start don't even be embarrassed. I mean, it's good stuff
Thing that is that you're haven't had one in a long time. My god, they're not system. Oh my god, like hell
That's 666. Oh my gosh. It's for sure. I know it's for sure. Okay. Well, I haven't look what I have though
You know, you're making fun of my first shirt, right? It's actually do you know how much I
Actual like you tried to like buy a shirt made of cat hair. You know how much it would cost
Thousands of dollars. Okay. I have it for free already, but look what I have
I have this like little mini roller too and it will look you know, just like like magic like what I do is like put this little roller on
I'm gonna have to wash your clothes anymore.
Just use this little blip roller
and it just cleans your clothes like magic.
Watch this, like a brand fresh new sheet.
You just put your store on the floor.
It's fine.
I'll pick it up later.
Okay, so you look at the orange and birch shirt.
Hey, birch shirt.
Is my shirt gonna look good?
Birch shirt?
Oh, look.
Look, it's like magic.
It's amazing.
It's like a dollar.
A dollar like those things.
Like, it took up most of the fur.
Oh my god, it's covered in cat fur.
And then I'm gonna make a wig out of the hair that I get
and I'm gonna sell it to PureLoveDog and BigKey0002.
Is that a proof thing on your face or your eye where you like me?
There's no proof thing, you know, the proof stain is in your brain. You're you know, you know
You know my tigger was looking in your toilet. He's looking for poo. You know what?
He didn't buy it because you were in the living room at the time. Okay guys. I'll talk to you guys later. Hey ghost I
Love you. I'll talk to you soon. Bye guys